{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"1030","name":"Carstens at Remus Robinson School","address":"13000 Essex St","zipcode":"48215","owner":"BRD OF EDUCATION DETROIT CITY","licenseNumber":"035085","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Public School","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"210","coords":"-82.94783,42.36366","geojson":{"id":"1030","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-82.9478304,42.363659128]},"properties":{"name":"Carstens at Remus Robinson School","owner":"BRD OF EDUCATION DETROIT CITY","address":"13000 Essex St","zipcode":"48215","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"035085","establishmentid":"1030","establishment_type":"Public School","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"210","most_recent_license_date":"6/1/2020"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"4537","name":"Govinda's at the Fisher Mansion","address":"383 Lenox Ave","zipcode":"48215"},{"establishmentid":"4927","name":"Davis Aerospace Tech High @ Golightly Te","address":"900 Dickerson Ave","zipcode":"48215"},{"establishmentid":"1388","name":"Golightly  Career Tech","address":"900 Dickerson Ave","zipcode":"48215"},{"establishmentid":"1711","name":"Dynasty Chinese","address":"13340 E Jefferson Ave","zipcode":"48215"},{"establishmentid":"1961","name":"Subway 12011","address":"13222 E Jefferson Ave","zipcode":"48215"},{"establishmentid":"5148","name":"Detroits Finest Coney Island","address":"13337 E Jefferson Ave. ","zipcode":"48215"},{"establishmentid":"424","name":"Bayview Yacht Club","address":"100 Clairpoint St","zipcode":"48215"},{"establishmentid":"51623025","name":"Bayview Yacht - Queen City","address":"100 Clairpointe St","zipcode":"48215"},{"establishmentid":"51623141","name":"Yellow Light Coffee & Donuts","address":"14447 E Jefferson Ave. ","zipcode":"48215"},{"establishmentid":"51622576","name":"Gingerberry LLC","address":"12626 E Jefferson Avenue","zipcode":"48215"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"53241","inspectionDate":"2020-10-29T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"Under the Condenser","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-204.11","violationDescription":"Exhaust ventilation hood systems in FOOD preparation and WAREWASHING areas including components such as hoods, fans, guards, and ducting shall be designed to prevent grease or condensation from draining or dripping onto FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Exhaust ventilation hood system(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Designed to allow grease or condensation from draining/dripping onto","subProblem":"Equipment","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Missing Grease collection device","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to prevent grease accumulation/dripping/draining."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"ceiling","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Ceiling tile(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"48090","inspectionDate":"2019-06-14T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-501.17","violationDescription":"A toilet room used by females shall be provided with a covered receptacle for sanitary napkins.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Covered waste receptacle(s)","subItem":"in ladies restroom","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (WOMEN'S)","subLocation":"No Covered waste container","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"At the Condenser","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"42532","inspectionDate":"2018-06-14T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-701.11","violationDescription":"(A) A FOOD that is unsafe, ADULTERATED, or not honestly presented as specified under § 3-101.11 shall be discarded or reconditioned according to an APPROVED procedure. (P)   \r\n(B) FOOD that is not from an APPROVED source as specified under \r\n§§ 3-201.11 - .17 shall be discarded. (P)   \r\n(C) READY-TO-EAT FOOD that may have been contaminated by an EMPLOYEE who has been RESTRICTED or EXCLUDED as specified under § 2-201.12 shall be discarded. (P) \r\n(D) FOOD that is contaminated by FOOD EMPLOYEES, CONSUMERS, or other PERSONS through contact with their hands, bodily discharges, such as nasal or oral discharges, or other means shall be discarded. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Contaminated food(s)","subItem":"food contaminated by by restricted or excluded employee","problemDescription":"Not discarded","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT PREP AREA","subLocation":"Inside the Cooler (milk)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-06-14T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN FREEZER","subLocation":"Inside the Walk-in freezer","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."}]},{"inspectionid":"40767","inspectionDate":"2017-11-09T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"at 30 inches above the floor","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER & FREEZER","subLocation":"At the Lights","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN FREEZER","subLocation":"At the Window frames","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN FREEZER","subLocation":"Inside the Walk-in freezer","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"39076","inspectionDate":"2017-06-16T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\r\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\r\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Missing","subProblem":"","location":"SCHOOL","subLocation":"At the PERSON IN CHARGE","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."}]},{"inspectionid":"37406","inspectionDate":"2016-12-15T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Drainage system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not constructed, designed, installed according to law","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"At the Three compartment sink","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove and replace to be in compliance with law."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2020-10-30T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"1030"}}